<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
   <name>More Monster Girls Enhanced Patch</name>
   <author>wagon</author>
   <supportedVersions>
      <li>1.0</li>
      <li>1.1</li>
      <li>1.2</li>
      <li>1.3</li>
      <li>1.4</li>
   </supportedVersions>
   <packageId>moremonstergirls.enhanced.rw</packageId>
   <description>Enhanced version of wagon's MoreMonstergirls updated for 1.1, and patched for various mods.

This is the Enhanced version, a different version than the only one that has been available on steam and patched for 1.0, where monster girls that have finished their obedience training can help with some work.

Monstergirls that have finished Obedience training can:
- Clean
- Mine
- Cut Plants
- Slaughter marked creatures
- Strip marked people

Mind it only work in the home area.

Of course, they can haul too when the training is done.

This is working for all monster girls that have advanced intelligence; which means all of them besides Slimes.

Finally, they will produce different products like milk, eggs, wool and feathers for you to benefit from; where the Slime produce Red Goo that can be used like an herbal medicine, 
and the fairies produce some dust than can be used as a drug.


I've made the mod compatible with Combat Extended (you do not need the mod; you can play without it if you don't want to use it), and also added compatibility with A dog Said mod. 
You just need to have A Dog Said, and LBE's A Dog Said Easy Patcher mods, and it will automatically work.

Loading order:
- CORE
- More Monster Girls - 1.1
- More Monster Girls Enhanced Patch - 1.1

All credit due to the original author of this mod, wagon!
</description>
<modDependencies>
    <li>
        <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
        <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
        <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
        <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
    <li>
        <packageId>moremonstergirls.rw</packageId>
        <displayName>More Monster Girls</displayName>
        <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2014838309</steamWorkshopUrl>
        <downloadUrl>https://github.com/KiameV/rimworld-moremonstergirls/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
</modDependencies>
<loadAfter>
	<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
	<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
	<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
	<li>moremonstergirls.rw</li>
</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>

